(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-15T21:59:06.914388",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
ATTENTION ご来場のお客様へ
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください／声出し応援 OK です
[ATTENTION] Notice to Visitors:
Beware of flashing lights / Loud cheering allowed
アニメにハマって 歌いたくなっちゃった
I got so hooked on anime that I just had to sing!
推しのシーン見ながら カラオケ歌えるなんて…
Being able to sing karaoke while watching scenes of my fave...
尊すぎてツライ！
It's so precious, I can't take it!
歌いたい曲見つけよう！
Find the songs you want to sing!
JOYSOUND！
JOYSOUND!
ReGLOSS 2nd Album 「Snapshot」の
ReGLOSS's 2nd album "Snapshot"...
レコードとカセットテープが
...will be available on vinyl and cassette tape!
2026年2月25日より HMV限定で発売決定しました！
Releasing exclusively at HMV on February 25, 2026!
12月17日までに ご予約いただくと
Pre-order by December 17th...
期間限定予約特典として スマホサイズステッカーをプレゼント！
...to get a smartphone-sized sticker as a limited-time bonus!
さらに抽選で5名様に サイン入りポスターをプレゼント！
Plus, 5 lucky pre-orders will win a signed poster!
「HMV ReGLOSS レコード カセット」で検索！
Search for "HMV ReGLOSS Vinyl Cassette"!
以上、ReGLOSSでした〜！
That's all from ReGLOSS!
紙細工の花びらを
Petals made of paper...
ある人は美しいと呟いた
someone murmured that they were beautiful.
この地球の横顔は
How does the profile of this Earth...
どう見えてる？キミの世界では
look in your world?
現実を逆さまにして
Turning reality upside down,
失くしそうなモノだけ振り落とした ah
I shook off only the things I might lose, ah
手のひらで拾い上げようとしたら
When I tried to scoop them up in my palm,
指の隙間すり抜け消えてった
they slipped through my fingers and vanished.
“形あるものだけが
"Tangible things aren't...
すべてじゃないけど
everything, but...
形あるものが
tangible things are...
どうしても欲しいよ”
what I desperately want."
この世界を変えることは
Changing this world...
きっとできないけど
is surely impossible, but...
キミの中の世界なら変えられるはず
the world inside you should be able to change.
芽吹いて咲いて実って枯れて
Budding, blooming, bearing fruit, and withering,
何ひとつ欠かせないから
because not a single thing is missing,
最後にキミが笑ってくれれば
if you smile in the end,
もうそれだけでいい
that alone will be enough.
言葉の彩を紡ぐ人
Those who weave the shades of words,
優しさを編む人
those who knit kindness,
それぞれの正義を
I want to unravel...
解いてあげたい
their respective sense of justice.
絡まった矛盾と
Entangled contradictions...
辻褄合わせ
and forcing logic to fit,
そんな刹那を抱え
holding onto such moments...
今日を生きている
we live today.
分け合った灯り
The lights we shared,
隣から隣へ
passing from one to another,
やがてひとつに
soon becoming one,
夜の帳へ
into the veil of night.
息を吹き込んだ
Breathed life into it,
キミとじゃなきゃだめなんだ ah
it has to be with you, ah.
このまま寝てしまうには
Falling asleep like this...
もったいないほど
would be such a waste,
優しさに包まれた夜だった
it was a night wrapped in kindness.
はっきり浮かび上がった夢の輪郭
The clearly emerged outline of a dream,
それは確かに愛だった
that was truly love.
ツキが見守る今夜
Tonight, watched over by the moon,
そっと一瞬を抱き締めた
I gently embraced the moment.
煌めく星
Sparkling stars,
色や形 温度や意味
colors, shapes, warmth, and meaning,
まるで何もかも違うボクらだけど
though we seem completely different in every way,
きっと最後にはこの音で繋がってる
in the end, we're surely connected by this sound.
ATTENTION ご来場のお客様へ
[Notice: Information for Visitors]
この世界を変えることは
Changing this world...
きっとできないけど
is surely impossible, but...
キミの中の世界なら変えられるはず
the world inside you should be able to change.
芽吹いて咲いて実って枯れて
Budding, blooming, bearing fruit, and withering,
何ひとつ欠かせないから
because not a single thing is missing,
最後にキミが笑ってくれれば
if you smile in the end,
もうそれだけでいい
that alone will be enough.
I'll always be by your side
紙細工の花びらを
Petals made of paper...
ある人は美しいと呟いた
someone murmured that they were beautiful.
この地球の横顔は
How does the profile of this Earth...
どう見えてる？キミの世界では
look in your world?
現実を逆さまにして
Turning reality upside down,
失くしそうなモノだけ振り落とした ah
I shook off only the things I might lose, ah
手のひらで拾い上げようとしたら
When I tried to scoop them up in my palm,
指の隙間すり抜け消えてった
they slipped through my fingers and vanished.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[Notice: The concert will be starting soon]
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
[Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance]
声出し応援 OK です
[Cheering loudly is OK]
本日は ReGLOSS 1st Live
Thank you for attending ReGLOSS 1st Live...
「Flashpoint」にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
..."Flashpoint" today!
みんなー！
Everyone!
いくぞー！
Here we go!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure you enjoy the live performance until the end, we have a few announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, audio recording, and video equipment are strictly prohibited during the show.
万が一、体調が悪くなってしまった場合は無理をせず、近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
If you happen to feel unwell, please don't push yourself and inform a nearby staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく跳びはねる、ステージに...
Inside the venue, mashing, diving, jumping excessively, on stage...
大丈夫、大丈夫！
It's okay, it's okay!
すみませんね
Sorry about that!
収録とかじゃないんでね！
It's not like a recorded broadcast!
緊張しちゃってごめんなさい
I'm sorry, I got nervous!
緊張しちゃうよね。もう一回言ってくださいね
Anyone would get nervous. Please say it one more time.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく跳びはねる、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、
Mosh pits, diving, jumping excessively, throwing objects onto the stage,
他のみんなの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
or any actions that cause trouble for others or disrupt the performance are strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Please follow the rules and have a great time!
まっちゃん
Macchan!
本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合がございます。
Cameras for video streaming and photography are present, and audience members may appear on screen.
映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please be aware in advance that footage and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
ライブのハッシュタグは #リグロス1stライブ です！
The hashtag for this show is #ReGLOSS1stLive!
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてください！
Please use the hashtag to help hype up the event!
それでは開演までもう少々！
Now, there's just a little time left until the show begins!
盛り上がる準備はできてますかー？！
Are you all ready to get hyped up?!
みんなで一緒に盛り上がるぞー！
Let's all turn up together!
以上、ReGLOSSでしたー！
That's all from ReGLOSS!
上級計画 プラウェット Welcome people
Advanced plan, play wet, welcome people
A-link B-link 来るゲート 希望
A-link, B-link, incoming gate, hope
どんな視線も釘付け Pretty girl
Captivating every gaze, pretty girl
一人じゃ足りない この声より...
One is not enough, more than this voice...
言い回しは慣れているけれど 妙に面白い服
I'm used to the phrasing, but these clothes are oddly interesting
胸踊る巡り合いは 一期一会
An exciting encounter is a once-in-a-lifetime chance
忘れないように 全部冷たさで包み込む
Wrapping everything in coldness so I won't forget
うつろい色あせるように
Fading away as if losing its color
春が来た... 蜃気楼
Spring has come... Mirage
蜃気楼 最低で儚いね 笑って SOS
Mirage, so awful and fleeting, laugh it off, SOS
踊ってみた そんなアルゴリズムの中で
Inside an algorithm like "I tried dancing"
失速して旅して 酔いがさめるまで
Decelerating and traveling until sobriety returns
蜃気楼...
Mirage...
立ちあがるもの...
Those who rise...
この世界を... 愛す言葉...
Words to love... this world...
君の中の世界なら 変えられるはず
If it's the world inside of you, it should be able to change
目をつむって 咲いて実って 惹かれて
Close your eyes, bloom, bear fruit, and be drawn in
最高に君が笑ってくれれば もうそれだけでいい
As long as you smile your brightest, that's all I need
音乃瀬奏
[Otonose Kanade]
一条莉々華
[Ichijou Ririka]
儒烏風亭らデン
[Juufuutei Raden]
轟はじめ
[Todoroki Hajime]
Flashpoint - ReGLOSS 1st Live
なぁ...
Hey...
My heart あげるから Me に
I'll give you my heart, so give yours to me.
決まった信条？
Is that a set creed?
さあ 曲がりくねって行こうぜ
Come on, let's take a winding path.
全然悪くないイマジネーション
That's not a bad imagination at all.
未来の送り手は晴れ渡って
The sender of the future clears up,
悲しみには別れを告げる
bidding farewell to sadness.
Sweet My Mind 散り散り放り出して
Sweet My Mind, throwing it all to the wind,
滲む空 ピンクは薔薇色
in the blurred sky, pink turns rose-colored.
どれだけ描いて見せようとしても
No matter how much I try to picture it,
君がいなければ何の意味もない
without you, it has no meaning at all.
擦り傷すらつかない幻想
An illusion without even a scratch,
針の落ちないレコードさ
like a record where the needle never drops.
喝采の途切れのない追い風にして
Turning the endless applause into a tailwind,
カモンレッツゴー
come on, let's go!
吹き荒れる向かい風にも負けず
Undeterred by the blowing headwind,
なびかせて
letting it flutter in the breeze.
飛び出せ To The Future
Jump into the future!
フライングしたって オーライ リスタート＆ライツ
Even a false start is okay, restart & lights!
ときめいてしまえば
Once your heart starts throbbing,
瞬く間に広がる解放区
a sanctuary spreads in the blink of an eye.
一つ一つすべてがパノラマ
Each and every piece is a panorama.
眩しい未来へ リスタート＆ライツ
Toward a dazzling future, restart & lights!
変わる世界のパノラマ
A panorama of a changing world,
満ち溢れる フィーリング＆テンション
overflowing with feeling & tension.
始まりの
The beginning...
その時が来た
...that moment has come.
Nothing is impossible
目をごまかし 惹かれてかい
Tricking your eyes, drawn in?
常識なんて 誰も知らない世界
Common sense? A world nobody knows yet.
妄想してるだけじゃ 始まらない
Just fantasizing won't start anything.
リアルタイムで ぶつかり合って
Clashing into each other in real-time.
理由に欠ければ All right
If you lack a reason, it's all right.
悪目立ちでも I don't mind
Even if I stand out for the wrong reasons, I don't mind.
ガムシャラに抱く熱情
Holding wild passion frantically,
どこまで行ってみようか
how far shall we try to go?
正解のない Girls forward
With no right answers, Girls forward!
共に声を鳴らせ
Ring out your voices together.
肌を貫く 凶暴なまっすぐな痛みが
Even if a ferocious, direct pain
伴っても
pierces right through your skin,
この仲間たちと 最果てまで
with these friends, to the very end,
Keep running to the end
飛び出せ To The Future
Jump into the future!
フライングしたって オーライ リスタート＆ライツ
Even a false start is okay, restart & lights!
ときめいてしまえば
Once your heart starts throbbing,
瞬く間に広がる解放区
a sanctuary spreads in the blink of an eye.
一つ一つすべてがパノラマ
Each and every piece is a panorama.
眩しい未来へ リスタート＆ライツ
Toward a dazzling future, restart & lights!
変わる世界のパノラマ
A panorama of a changing world,
満ち溢れる フィーリング＆テンション
overflowing with feeling & tension.
飛び出せ You and me yeah
Jump out, You and me yeah!
恐れるものは何もない リスタート＆ライツ
There's nothing to fear, restart & lights!
透明な明日を変えて行く
We will change the transparent tomorrow.
リスタート＆ライツ
Restart & lights!
皆さん、こんにちはー！
Hello, everyone!
ReGLOSS 3Dライブ "In-between" へようこそお越しくださいましたー！
Welcome to the ReGLOSS 3D Live "In-between"!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
本日は皆さん楽しんでいって、素敵な一夜にいたしましょう！
Let's all have fun today and make it a wonderful night!
本日は生バンドでお届けいたします！盛り上がっていきましょう！
Today we're performing with a live band! Let me hear you get hyped!
みんなー！次の曲は ノリノリの曲！
Everyone! The next song is super upbeat!
盛り上がる準備はいいですかー？
Are you ready to get hyped?
みんなで ドキドキ してね！
Get excited, everyone!
Oki Doki ギザサイコー オンナノコ
Oki Doki, super awesome girls!
1 2 3 最大級 Try to say my favorite
1 2 3, maximum size! Try to say my favorite.
Oki Doki そのままで居たいよね
Oki Doki, you want to stay as you are, right?
1 2 3 踊ろうよ Everybody
1 2 3, let's dance, Everybody!
それそれ重ねて ガチガチの
Layering each one on top, stiff and solid,
宇宙船乗り込み 混ざり合おう
let's jump into the spaceship and blend together!
たまには無邪気になって
Sometimes, just be innocent.
ノープランでいいんじゃない？
Isn't having no plan totally fine?
ここから始まる
Starting right from here,
愉快な仲間と Make some noise!
with our fun friends, Make some noise!
無駄話も一通り
All sorts of random chatter,
バカ言わん！
Don't talk nonsense!
運命 境界 伝染して
Destiny, boundary, spreading out,
行く気のない Love
a Love with no intention of leaving.
分かち合える Empathy 共に目指すは
Sharing empathy, aiming together for...
Reach the top, yeah!
絶対 絶対 絶対 絶対 ギラギラ中
Definitely, definitely, definitely, definitely gleaming bright!
今は自由気ままに
Right now, freely as we please,
居心地のいい
in this comfortable...
この Universe
...Universe!
凛々しく 凛々しく 進行するシナリオ
A scenario progressing with grace and dignity.
限界突破 引き付けるミラクル
Breaking through limits, attracting miracles!
皆さーん！ペンライト良く見えてますよー！
Everyone! We can see your penlights really well!
次は... まだもっとブンブン振っていけー！
Next... keep waving them even harder!
いっくよー！
Here we go!
Oki Doki ギザサイコー オンナノコ
Oki Doki, super awesome girls!
Easy Breezy Try to say my favorite
Oki Doki そのままで居たいよね
Oki Doki, you want to stay as you are, right?
Easy Breezy 踊ろうよ Everybody
Easy Breezy, let's dance, Everybody!
ひとりつまずいたら またひとりにむつみあう
When one stumbles, we cuddle close again.
温かい気持ち Kata-Sumi-No-Mono-Rogue
A warm feeling, a monologue in the corner.
もう終了時間 あっという間の stream
It's already ending time, the stream went by in a flash.
みんなといる空間が extreme
Being in this space with everyone is extreme!
量産する掛け替えのない memories
Creating tons of irreplaceable memories,
遮二無二 掴み取る next dream
recklessly snatching up our next dream.
運命共同体
Bound together by fate,
感染してゆく喜怒哀楽
all our emotions spread and infect one another.
分かち合えるエンパシー
Empathy we can share...
共に目指すは
Together, what we aim for is...
Reach the top yeah!
絶対絶対絶対絶対的キラーチューン
Absolute, absolute, absolute, absolute killer tune!
今は自由気まま 水入らずなユニバース
Right now we're carefree, an intimate universe just for us.
Reload re reload reload シンクロするシナプス
Reload, re-reload, reload, syncing up our synapses!
限界突破 惹きつけるミラクル
Breaking through limits, drawing in miracles!
Okey dokey 史上最高な
Okey-dokey, the best ever...
Easy breezy 歌い出せば favorite
Easy breezy, once we start singing, it's our favorite!
Okey dokey このままでいたいよね
Okey-dokey, we want to stay like this forever, right?
Easy breezy 踊ろうよ everybody
Easy breezy, let's dance, everybody!
ReGLOSS 1st Live「FLASH POINT」へようこそ！
Welcome to ReGLOSS 1st Live "FLASH POINT"!
ようこそー！
Welcome!
いつもの挨拶から行きましょう！Reach the top! We are...
Let's start with our usual greeting! Reach the top! We are...
ReGLOSS!
では早速自己紹介からしていきたいと思います！
Now then, let's start with our self-introductions!
はい！感度良好、アニソン歌うの超大好き！
Yeah! Signal crystal clear, loving to sing anime songs!
音乃瀬奏です！
I'm Otonose Kanade!
たまご豆腐〜 体中で〜
Egg tofu~ with all your body~
みんな愛してくれていいよ〜！あ、黄色になってる！ありがとう！
feel free to love me all you want~! Ah, you turned your lightsticks yellow! Thank you!
そして！可愛い、ポジティブ、ジーニアス！
And! Cute, positive, genius!
リリカです！一条莉々華だよ〜！
I'm Lirika! Ichijou Ririka here~!
やばい、もうみんなの声めっちゃ今浴びてる今！
Oh my gosh, I'm soaking in everyone's cheers right now!
めっちゃ嬉しい！ありがとう！最高な気分！そして！
I'm so happy! Thank you! Feeling amazing! And next!
はい、えー、ホロライブDEV_IS ReGLOSSの賑やか賑やかしネタ作り担当
Yes, um, in charge of lively hype and jokes for Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS,
前座見習い 儒烏風亭らでんでございます。本日はどうぞよろしくお願い申し上げます！
opening act apprentice Juufuutei Raden here. Thank you so much for having me today!
最後は〜
And last but not least~
はい！ブッブッブー！フライト前チェック！
Yes! Beep-beep-beep! Pre-flight check!
ちーちゃん、はじめ、つみれタン、こんちくわ〜！
Chi-chan, Hajime, Tsumire-tan, konchikuwa~!
こんちくわ〜！
Konchikuwa~!
紫ありがっちょ〜！
Thank you for the purple lightsticks~!
ありがとう〜！ついに始まりました！
Thank you~! It's finally started!
ReGLOSS 1st Live！
ReGLOSS 1st Live!
なんと！会場は満員！
What a surprise! The venue is packed!
キャー！超立派ー！
Kyaa! So magnificent~!
こんなにたくさんのグロスターが集まってくれましたー！
So many GLOSS-STARs have gathered here today~!
すごい！もう最高の景色ですよ！
Amazing! It's such a breathtaking view!
皆さん、本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you all so very much!
想い想いのファッションとかもね...
Seeing everyone's unique outfits and style...
本当にありがとうございます！今日は最後まで思いっきり楽しんでまいりましょう！
Thank you so much! Let's enjoy ourselves to the fullest until the very end today!
そしてね、会場だけじゃなくて...
And you know, it's not just the live venue...
配信もされております！配信の皆タン、楽しんでますか〜？
it's also being livestreamed! Is everyone on the stream having fun~?
配信の皆タン〜！イエーイ！
Everyone watching the stream~! Yay!
そしてそして！韓国ではライブビューイングが実施されています！
And also, live viewings are taking place in Korea!
アンニョンハセヨ〜！
Annyeonghaseyo~!
ライブビューイングをご覧の皆さん、楽しくご覧ですか〜？
To everyone watching at the live viewings, are you enjoying the show~?
すごい！奏！
Incredible, Kanade!
すごいじゃないよ！当たり前だろ！
Don't just say "incredible"! It's second nature to me!
はい！ということで、早速ですが今立っているこのステージ...
Right! So, straight to the point, instead of this stage we're standing on right now...
ではなく、なんと2階からの登場でございましたが、皆さんびっくりした？どうだった？
we actually made our grand entrance from the 2nd floor! Was everyone surprised? How was it?
びっくりしたー！
We were surprised~!
オープニングから『フィーリングラデーション』、そして『bvdiz』と2曲続けてお披露目させていただきましたが、皆さんいかがでしたでしょうかー？
From the opening, we performed "Feeling Gradation" and then "bvdiz", two songs back-to-back! How did you all like it?
どう？どう？
How was it? How was it?
えー、そしてね！皆タンもうお気づきかと思いますけども...
And also! I'm sure everyone has already noticed...
今回のライブはバンドメンバーと一緒にお届けしています！
we're performing today together with a live band!
かっこいい！
So cool!
普段聴いてるあの曲がどんなアレンジになるのか、お楽しみに〜！
Look forward to seeing what kind of live arrangements those familiar songs will get~!
はい！今日の感想や心に残った瞬間は...
Yes! For your thoughts on today and memorable moments...
ハッシュタグ #ReGLOSS_1stLive でぜひポストしてください！
please post them using the hashtag #ReGLOSS_1stLive!
みんなの感想、後で我々見に行きますので、めちゃくちゃ楽しみです！よろしくお願いします！
We'll be checking everyone's posts later, so we're super excited! Thank you!
お願いしまーす！
Please do~!
さあ！それではね、早速ではございますが、次の曲に行きましょうか！
Alright! Now then, without further ado, shall we move on to the next song?
あ！でも待って待って！YouTubeやTikTokで見てくれてる皆さん！ごめんなさい！
Ah! Wait, wait, wait! To everyone watching on YouTube and TikTok! We're sorry!
無料配信はここまで！
The free stream ends here!
それ早いんだけど
That was fast, but
無料チラ見せパートはなんとですね、次の曲までとなっております！
the free preview section actually ends after the next song!
えー！？
Ehh~?!
まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたいみんなは、概要欄のリンクから見てください！
Everyone who wants to keep getting hyped up with us, please check the link in the description!
はーい！
Okay!
みんな〜
Everyone~
ライブはね、まだまだ始まったばかりですよ！
The concert has only just begun!
最後までね、一緒に最高の時間を過ごそう！
Let's spend the best time together until the end!
Snowfall 触れるチョーク
Snowfall, touching chalk...
幻想と過ち ノイズは鳴らし
Illusions and mistakes, noise echoing...
スローモーション 神様の所有
Slow motion, in God's possession
おどけてみせる銀世界 Yeah yeah yeah yeah
A silver world acting foolish, yeah yeah yeah yeah
If the sky is falling down
If the stars have no shine
真っ白な紙の上
On a pure white piece of paper
答え 滲ませ
Blurring the answers
すべて 思うままに
Everything just as we wish
風が刻む 波のメロディ
The wind carves the melody of waves
パンドラ パンドラ 夢を解き放ち
Pandora, Pandora, releasing dreams
移ろい 色褪せるように
Shifting, as if fading away
パンドラ パンドラ 秘密のオブジェクト
Pandora, Pandora, a secret object
シカブラ パンパンパンパンパンパン
Shikabura pan-pan-pan-pan-pan-pan
ガタガタ振るうスター
Rattling, trembling star
シカブラ パンパンパンパンパンパン
Shikabura pan-pan-pan-pan-pan-pan
灯す光 サイレンスプロウリング シカブラ
Lighting the spark, silence prowling, Shikabura
1クールのドラマよりも長いフェリーテール
A fairytale longer than a single-cour drama
嘘 偽りなくて This pain
No lies, no deceit, this pain
刺せよ 長いプラスティックのナイフ
Pierce through, long plastic knife
この世に表も裏もない
In this world, there is no front or back
いつも違う表情 おぼろげな愛論
Always a different expression, a hazy theory of love
一日を抱きしめてたいのに
Even though I want to embrace each day
沈む足元 怯む暇はない 上を目指そう
Sinking underfoot, no time to flinch, let's aim higher
In our world, where no one's at
曖昧の Happy and kind
Vague, happy and kind
忍ばせて仮初め
Hiding in disguise
朽ちるまで待ちぼうけ
Waiting in vain until decaying
偽れ 花になる
Feign it, turning into a flower
風が刻む 波のメロディ
The wind carves the melody of waves
パンドラ パンドラ 夢を解き放ち
Pandora, Pandora, releasing dreams
移ろい 色褪せるように
Shifting, as if fading away
パンドラ パンドラ 秘密のオブジェクト
Pandora, Pandora, a secret object
可能性が スリリングになって
Possibilities becoming thrilling
幾重にも重なって 試すキザみにアンビバレンス
Layered upon layers, ambivalence carved by testing
想像にほどいた 定め向かい風
Unraveled in imagination, destined headwind
今こそ切なる願い 打ち鳴らせ Wake up
Now is the earnest wish, strike and sound, wake up
そっと手を伸ばす 冬枯れの化粧
Gently reaching out, makeup of a withered winter
閉ざしてしまいそうな夜だって
Even on nights that seem ready to shut down
この歌声で繋ぎ止めてみせるから
I'll hold it together with this singing voice
風が刻む 波のメロディ
The wind carves the melody of waves
パンドラ パンドラ 夢を解き放ち
Pandora, Pandora, releasing dreams
移ろい 色褪せるように
Shifting, as if fading away
パンドラ パンドラ 秘密のオブジェクト
Pandora, Pandora, a secret object
シカブラ パンパンパンパンパンパン
Shikabura pan-pan-pan-pan-pan-pan
ガタガタ振るうスター
Rattling, trembling star
シカブラ パンパンパンパンパンパン
Shikabura pan-pan-pan-pan-pan-pan
灯す光 サイレンスプロウリング シカブラ
Lighting the spark, silence prowling, Shikabura
今日、僕らの
Today, our...
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview has ended. Thank you for watching!
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!